Marek Sadura

Senior Full Stack Javascript Engineer Lublin, Poland (GMT +2) linkedin.com/in/marek-sadura-epicode github.com/msadura sadura.mar@gmail.com +48 693737572 Software Engineer with over 10 years of professional experience in both front-end and back-end technologies. My aim is to develop software with the best quality, accessible UI, made user-first. Very enthusiastic about blockchain and web3 development.

Work Experience —

Senior Full Stack Engineer

THORSwap Finance - https://app.thorswap.finance

Jan 2022 - Current

- Implementing redesigned Decentralized Crypto Exchange interface using React, Redux, tailwindcss. Creating and delivering solution for Thorchain multisig wallet.
- Creating design system based on atomic components and storybook, considering mobile devices.
- · Actively improving UI and UX, based on experience refactoring existing logic to achieve long-term sustainability.
- Integrating interface with THORChain api, providing announcements Node.js service.
- · Implementing and designing lending interface
- Building Partners dashboard with wallet login, interactive charts and onchain data.

Main technologies: Typescript, React, NextJS, Ethersjs, Tailwind CSS, ChakraUl, Redux, Redux-toolkit, Node.js, tRPC, Prisma, PostgreSQL

Senior Javascript Developer

Sling by Toast - https://getsling.com

Feb 2017 - Jun 2022

- Introducing React to the project, rewriting AngularJS web app to React. Designing React app architecture.
- Leading on mobile app development in React Native for iOS and android devices. Building CI pipeline for releases using fastlane.
- Working on improving product UI and UX, using best code practises and building base components based on design system.

Main technologies: Typescript, React, React Native, Redux, Rxjs, Styled Components, Storybook, Jest, Mocha

Senior Software Developer

BLStream (rebranded to Intive)

Mar 2014 - Feb 2017

- Building the official Oscars website in AngularJS https://oscars.go.com/
- Implementing SEO friendly AngularJS app with pre-rendering content on the server.
- Working close to the customer, gathering requirements and implementing functionalities under the pressure of time.

Main technologies: Typescript, AngularJS, React, Mocha, Less, Redux, AWS

Software Developer

Select Sp. Z o.o.

Jun 2011 - Mar 2014

- Customizing ZenCart based ecommerce platforms.
- Supporting and expanding functionalities of CRM systems based on SugarCRM, introducing AngularJS to the project.
- Implementing designs and RWD interfaces.

Main technologies: PHP, MySQL, Javascript, CSSs, AngularJS, nginx

Projects

Memes Art Aug 2021 - Jun 2022

https://memes.art - web3 app that allows user to create a meme and generate it onchain as NFT. Own project used to learn Solidity basics. Built with React and Next.js, Solidity and hardhat.

Education